<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome to YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/first-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/first-account/</guid><description>When the application starts for the first time or when there aren&amp;rsquo;t any accounts, it will show the welcome page.
Tap the &amp;ldquo;New Account&amp;rdquo; to start the creation of your first account.
First Account Enter a name for the account. The name is only kept in your device. Choose the crypto Tap &amp;ldquo;New&amp;rdquo; Please make sure that you save the seed words when it reminds you. The seed words are the list of 24 words shown on the backup page.</description></item><item><title>UI Mode</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/ui_mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/ui_mode/</guid><description>By default, Ywallet runs in &amp;ldquo;Simple Mode&amp;rdquo; where only the basic UI elements are shown.
Account Information Messages Transaction History Contacts To show the rest of the UI, switch to &amp;ldquo;Advanced Mode&amp;rdquo; in the application settings</description></item><item><title>Account summary</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/account-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/account-summary/</guid><description>Shielded Mode Address QR Code Address (middle part elided) Copy address to clipboard Show address QR Code full screen without other data Account Balance (up to 1/1000 of a coin) Remaining part of the Account balance (below 1/1000 coin) Press to generate a new (diversified) address Press to go to the send page Balance in Fiat currency and Exchange Rate Notes Diversified (or snap addresses) show up for a few seconds.</description></item><item><title>Synchronization</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/synchronization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/synchronization/</guid><description>Synchronization (Catchup) will automatically start when YWallet detects that it does not have the latest block data.
Synchronization is complete when only the block height number is displayed above the QR code.
You can also manually trigger a rescan through the application menu.
Statistics During Rescan or Catchup, the blockheight will cycle between the following information:
current height / latest height synchronization % number of blocks remaining to process timestamp of latest block processed ETA (Estimated Time Remaining to complete the scan) Bytes downloaded from the server Number of transaction outputs decrypted Tapping on the display will alternate between cycling and a fixed display.</description></item><item><title>Receive coins</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/receive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/receive/</guid><description>The person who sends you coins needs to know your account address. There are several ways to communicate it.
The wallet shows the address on the account page, but it is long and unpractical to type it in. It is more practical to do one of the following:
Copy it to the clipboard and paste it into an email/chat
Tilt your device forward and let them scan your QR Code (your balance is hidden)</description></item><item><title>Send coins</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/send/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/send/</guid><description>Start from the account page by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo; button in the bottom right corner Address to send coins to Tap to open the QR code scanner Either enter the amount in mZEC or Enter the amount in Fiat currency. The other field updates automatically Tap to spend the entire balance Show/Collapse advanced options Tap to send. Detailed balances Total balance available = transparent + shielded Shielded NOTES that don&amp;rsquo;t have enough confirmations for sending Shielded notes that were excluded from sending (COIN CONTROL) Transparent balance.</description></item></channel></rss>