<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UI Mode</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/ui_mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/ui_mode/</guid><description>By default, Ywallet runs in &amp;ldquo;Simple Mode&amp;rdquo; where only the basic UI elements are shown.
Account Information Messages Transaction History Contacts To show the rest of the UI, switch to &amp;ldquo;Advanced Mode&amp;rdquo; in the application settings</description></item><item><title>Your first account</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/first-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/first-account/</guid><description>YWallet automatically creates the first account. Please make sure that you save the seed words when it reminds you. The seed words are the list of 24 words shown on the backup page. If you lose access to your phone or wallet, all you need are these words. But conversely, anyone with these words also has access to your funds.
The seed words must be kept in a safe place and away from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>Account summary</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/account-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/account-summary/</guid><description>Shielded Mode Address QR Code Address (middle part elided) Copy address to clipboard Show address QR Code full screen without other data Account Balance (up to 1/1000 of a coin) Remaining part of the Account balance (below 1/1000 coin) Press to generate a new (diversified) address Press to go to the send page Balance in Fiat currency and Exchange Rate Notes Diversified (or snap addresses) show up for a few seconds.</description></item><item><title>Receive coins</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/receive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/receive/</guid><description>The person who sends you coins needs to know your account address. There are several ways to communicate it.
The wallet shows the address on the account page, but it is long and unpractical to type it in. It is more practical to do one of the following:
Copy it to the clipboard and paste it into an email/chat
Tilt your device forward and let them scan your QR Code (your balance is hidden)</description></item><item><title>Send coins</title><link>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/send/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/getting-started/send/</guid><description>Start from the account page by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo; button in the bottom right corner Address to send coins to Tap to open the QR code scanner Either enter the amount in mZEC or Enter the amount in Fiat currency. The other field updates automatically Tap to spend the entire balance Show/Collapse advanced options Tap to send. Detailed balances Total balance available = transparent + shielded Shielded NOTES that don&amp;rsquo;t have enough confirmations for sending Shielded notes that were excluded from sending (COIN CONTROL) Transparent balance.</description></item></channel></rss>