<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced Usage on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced Usage on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Auto-Shield Transparent Balance</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/auto-shield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/auto-shield/</guid><description>The Auto-Shield feature automatically transfers your transparent balance to the shielded address when it is greater than a configurable amount.
It runs when it detects a change in your balance and schedules a transaction immediately.
Set the threshold in the settings.
Remarks If you set a low threshold, it may make a lot of transactions However, if the threshold is high, your transparent balance could remain unshielded for a long time Each transaction costs 0.</description></item><item><title>Coin Control</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/coin-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/coin-control/</guid><description>By default, every received note that has enough confirmations can be picked in an outgoing transaction. With Coin Control, you can exclude some notes from being selected.
Tap to select/deselect notes. Notes that are selected will not be spent</description></item><item><title>Send Options</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/advanced-send/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/advanced-send/</guid><description>Enable/Disable rounding to 0.001 coin. If rounding is disabled, the app uses zats: 1/100,000,000 of a coin If checked, the transaction will use the balance in the transparent address too Split Notes: The maximum amount per output note. If this is less than the amount sent, the app will create several notes. The change is not subject to this cap WARNING If the option to use the transparent balance is checked, the transaction will include the whole transparent balance.</description></item><item><title>Budget</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/budget/</guid><description>The budget page shows your largest spending/payments and a chart of your past account balance.
The table shows the top 5 addresses where you spent the most.
The length of each segment is proportional to its amount Address or Contact Name. Tap to copy the address to the clipboard Total amount sent to the address Tap and hold to show the exact balance at a given time The time range can be adjusted on the Settings page</description></item><item><title>Wallet Profit and Loss</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/pnl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/pnl/</guid><description>Wallet P/L (Profit and Loss) calculates and displays your wallet performance versus fiat currency. It considers incoming funds as purchases at market price and outgoing funds as sales.
For example, if you receive 1 ZEC when 1 ZEC=140 USD and then spend 0.5 ZEC when 1 ZEC=150 USD, your wallet performance will be:
0.5 x (150 - 140) of realized profit 0.5 x (150 - 140) of unrealized profit If later 1 ZEC=180 USD,</description></item><item><title>MultiPay</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/multipay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/multipay/</guid><description>MultiPay allows you to create a single payment transaction with multiple recipients.
Tap to add a recipient (&amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo;) Finish and send the transaction (&amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo;) Add a recipient After tapping the button &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo;
Adding a new recipient is done using the same entry form as a single recipient payment.
See Send Coins.
Remove Recipients Swipe the Recipient row left/right off the screen to discard it.
Send After pressing the button &amp;ldquo;Send&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Cold Storage</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/cold-storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/cold-storage/</guid><description>In a cold storage transaction, the mobile account does not have the secret key needed for spending. However, it is able to build an unsigned transaction and export it as a file.
The account owner moves the file to another computer that holds the secret key (preferably offline and air-gapped for security).
On the offline computer, he signs the transaction and generate a now valid transaction that he saves to another file.</description></item><item><title>Sub-Account</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/sub-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/sub-account/</guid><description>Main Account Your main account is displayed in bold face. There is one main account for each coin. When you spend and receive coins from the dashboard shortcuts, the funds will be directed to the main account.
The main account is the last account you selected for that particular coin.
Sub Accounts A seed phrase can derive a multitude of accounts. By default, Ywallet uses only the first account.</description></item><item><title>Custom Derivation Path</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/custom_path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/custom_path/</guid><description>For Transparent Addresses Only For a single account, it is easier to use the scan sub account feature.
If you have funds in a legacy wallet (pre NU-5) that hasn&amp;rsquo;t been upgraded to support transaction V5, your funds are inaccessible.
However, you can create an account in YWallet using the same seed phrase and derivation path.
The resulting secret key and address will be identical and you will be able to sweep your funds.</description></item><item><title>Batch Save/Load</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/batch-save/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/batch-save/</guid><description>Save all your Accounts Save the encryption key! Save the backup file The backup cannot be restored without the encryption key. Note: Every backup gets its unique encryption key (even if the accounts are the same)
Restore a full backup Enter or paste the encryption key Load the backup file</description></item><item><title>Reset</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/reset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/reset/</guid><description>After a major upgrade, the app may exhibit incorrect behavior. If this happens, the easiest way to fix the issue is to uninstall, reinstall and restore from seed.
You should always have a safe copy of your seed phrase
If your phone or computer crashes and you don&amp;rsquo;t have the seed phrase, your funds are LOST.
But if you really don&amp;rsquo;t have the seed phrase and the app is still working you can try resetting it by following the instructions below.</description></item><item><title>Import from ZecWallet Lite</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/zwl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/zwl/</guid><description>You can import your wallet keys from ZWL directly into YWallet without needing to synchronize ZWL.
This can be useful when ZWL fails to open.
ZecWallet Lite is not responsive until it is fully synced up. If your wallet cannot be synced, you will not be able to operate ZWL. For example, it may get appear stuck on the loading screen.
However, zecwallet-lite-cli the command line version of ZWL has an option to by-pass synchronization.</description></item><item><title>Key Tool</title><link>https://ywallet.app/advanced/keytool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/advanced/keytool/</guid><description>The Key Tool is a transparent &amp;amp; secret key derivation tool based on BIP32/39/44 and ZIP32.
It is similar to the Mnemonic Code Converter but built specifically for Zcash and Ycash.
With the Key Tool, you can extract the private keys of most (all?) wallets, as long as they use a seed phrase.
Ledger, Coinomi, Edge, Nighthawk, ZecWallet Lite Zcash (HDSeed), etc. However, the derivation path they use varies from wallet to wallet.</description></item></channel></rss>