<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accounts on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/</link><description>Recent content in Accounts on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 04:38:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/overview/</guid><description>Y/ZWallet supports one or many accounts. Each account has a shielded and transparent address (unless it was restored from a secret key).
An address has zero or more notes. For shielded accounts, notes are encrypted and only visible to the account owner. Transparent addresses have notes in cleartext.
A note is conceptually an &amp;ldquo;I Owe You&amp;rdquo;. It can have any amount greater than zero (including zero). The account balance is the sum of all the note amounts.</description></item><item><title>Account Manager</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/manager/</guid><description>Open the account manager by selecting &amp;ldquo;Accounts&amp;rdquo; in the app menu.
Currency Name Total Balance Shielded Balance Transparent Balance Long Press to Edit Name Swipe left/right to Delete Add/Restore Account To return to the account page, select an account by tapping on its name. Or press the back button, if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to change the current selection.
Add Account Press the Button &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; in the bottom right corner.</description></item><item><title>Adding More Accounts</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/add/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/add/</guid><description>Press the button + in the bottom right corner. It opens the account creation and restoration page. Choose the currency Give a name to your new account. But leave the field &amp;ldquo;Seed/Secret Key/Viewing Key&amp;rdquo; empty for a new account. Press the button &amp;ldquo;NEW&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;. The app will show the account backup information. Your backup is the 24 words in the top box. You must keep these words in a safe place.</description></item><item><title>Backup Restore</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/restore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/restore/</guid><description>Backup Backups are very important and must be taken unless you don&amp;rsquo;t mind losing access to the account and the coins it contains.
Fortunately, it is very easy to make a backup.
The account backup is the 24 words (in sequence) displayed on the Backup page (seed phrase)
When you create a new account, the app will show you the Backup page automatically. If you need to recall that page, open the app menu and select &amp;ldquo;Backup&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Notes</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/notes/</guid><description>The Note Tab shows your received notes.
Display and Sorting Tap to toggle the display of Height or Number of Confirmations Tap to sort by Date/Time (switches between ascending, descending, and unsorted) Tap to sort by Amount Larger notes appear in bolder typeface Status Notes spent in unconfirmed transactions are crossed out Notes that don&amp;rsquo;t have enough confirmations (3 by default) are dimmed Navigation Current Page Go to First Page Previous Page Next Page Go to Last Page Adjust the Number of rows per page.</description></item><item><title>Payment URI</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/payment_uri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/payment_uri/</guid><description>The Receive/Payment URI page is for making QR codes that encode
your receiving address (shielded or transparent) an amount requested in coins or in fiat currency and a memo text Once you fill these fields, tap the &amp;ldquo;Make QR&amp;rdquo; button to update the QR code. If you don&amp;rsquo;t tap the button, the QR code is just your receiving address. You can also tap the QR code to refresh it.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/transactions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/transactions/</guid><description>The History Tab shows the transaction history.
Tap to toggle the display of height / confirmations Tap to sort by Date/Time (switches between ascending, descending, and unsorted) Tap to sort by Amount Tap to sort by Transaction ID Current page range Go to First Page Previous Page Next Page Go to Last Page Adjust the Number of rows per page. You may have to scroll the footer to the left if your screen is too small.</description></item><item><title>Synchronization</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/sync/</guid><description>The app keeps up to date with the blockchain automatically. It checks the current status of the blockchain every 15s.
Rescan You can manually trigger a rescan.
Either from the first block, or from a given date (1).
Scan Progress Status Current block height being processed Latest block height The Estimated remaining time of the full scan When the app is synchronized with the current block, it just displays the block height.</description></item><item><title>Watch Only</title><link>https://ywallet.app/account/watch-only/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/account/watch-only/</guid><description>You can turn a regular account into a watch-only account. This prevents you or anyone from spending from it. You will still be able to receive coins and monitor the balance.
Making an account watch-only is NOT reversible and you must have a backup of the seed phrase to restore the account later.
Select the Cold Storage option from the app menu Choose &amp;ldquo;DELETE&amp;rdquo;</description></item></channel></rss>