<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Messages on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/</link><description>Recent content in Messages on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/messages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Message List</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/center/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/messages/center/</guid><description>Messages are contained in the memo field. Whenever you send to a shielded address, you can attach some data through the memo.
Memos have a maximum size of 512 bytes which is enough in most cases.
Message List Avatar of the Sender or Recipient. The color depends on their initial Sender or Receiver and the direction (out/in) Date/Time Subject. Unread messages are shown in bold Content Tap to send a new message Message Table The Message Table is shown if you have selected it in the settings.</description></item><item><title>Message Details</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/details/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/messages/details/</guid><description>Navigation Go to the previous message in same thread (i.e. same subject) Go to the previous message Go to the next message Go to the next message in same thread (i.e. same subject) Reply If the message has a sender, click on this button to reply to it. It will open a send dialog box with the subject and recipient prepopulated.</description></item><item><title>Send a Message</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/send/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/messages/send/</guid><description>Send Sending a message is done through the regular &amp;ldquo;Send YEC/ZEC&amp;rdquo; dialog box.
Check if you want to include your address Subject Body You can also attach some coins with the message.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/messages/settings/</guid><description>Settings The only new setting for Messages is the option to include your address by default. If enabled, the send dialog box will have this option pre-checked.</description></item><item><title>Internal Format</title><link>https://ywallet.app/messages/internal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/messages/internal/</guid><description>In order to support messages with subject and sender, YWallet formats the memo field in a particular way. Other wallets will see messages as this:
🛡MSG ys19xxuxdrw07fjz6j0u0cfcfeczg04pfupcm7pae0tyy4qn0wzmsp87nntfmlkxu2tcqz4xsy9exf hey Wanna get brunch on Sunday? The first line 🛡MSG indicates that it is a YWallet shielded message. The second line is the address of the sender. The later may choose to remain anonymous, in which case this line is empty. The third line is the subject of the message.</description></item></channel></rss>